<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<resources>
  <string name="AVL">AVL</string>
  <string name="Avast">Avast</string>
  <string name="DesAVL">AVL</string>
  <string name="DesAvast">Avast</string>
  <string name="DesMi">Mi</string>
  <string name="DesTencent">Tencent</string>
  <string name="Mi">Mi</string>
  <string name="Tencent">Tencent</string>
  <string name="app_name">Componentes de Segurança MIUI</string>
  <string name="avast_dialog_cloudscan"/>
  <string name="avast_dialog_dbupdate"/>
  <string name="avast_dialog_header">Esta funcionalidade encripta e envia o seu ID de dispositivo para os servidores Avast (%s)</string>
  <string name="avast_dialog_policy">Ver Política de Privacidade</string>
  <string name="avast_dialog_title">Política de Privacidade de Avast</string>
  <string name="avast_dialog_url">http://api.sec.miui.com/policy/proxy?p=avast&amp;l=en_US</string>
  <string name="avast_virus_type_adware_description">Este vírus é um adware. Mostra anúncios automaticamente</string>
  <string name="avast_virus_type_cryportor_description">Este vírus é um cryptor. É um software malicioso que se replica no espaço de armazenamento</string>
  <string name="avast_virus_type_dropper_description">Este vírus é um dropper. Carrega código que instala outros vírus</string>
  <string name="avast_virus_type_exploit_description">Este vírus é um exploit. It takes advantage of a bug or vulnerability in system in order to cause unintended or unanticipated behavior.</string>
  <string name="avast_virus_type_heuristic_description">The infection is inferred by using a specific heuristic. A specific heuristic analysis says that it is a virus.</string>
  <string name="avast_virus_type_joke_description">Este vírus é um joke. It creates some annoying or humorous effect as a joke. It normally has less damage on the system.</string>
  <string name="avast_virus_type_pup_description">Este vírus é programa potencialmente não desejado (PUP). É um programa não desejado (como spyware, adware, etc), tirando o facto de que o utilizador dá o consentimento para o transferir</string>
  <string name="avast_virus_type_rootkit_description">Este vírus é um rootkit. It is a type of software designed to hide the fact that an operating system has been compromised. It is used to gain control over the device by hiding deep inside the system. Rootkits allow viruses and malware to “hide in plain sight” by disguising as necessary files that normal antivirus software will overlook.</string>
  <string name="avast_virus_type_spyware_description">"The virus is a spyware. It a software that covertly gathers user information through the user' Internet connection without his or her knowledge."</string>
  <string name="avast_virus_type_suspicious_description">A common suspicious type. The antivirus system is trying to classify it.</string>
  <string name="avast_virus_type_tool_description">The virus is a potentially evil tool infecting by means similar to PUP.</string>
  <string name="avast_virus_type_trjan_description">Este vírus é um trojan. It is a a malware designed to provide unauthorized, remote access to a user’s device. Trojans normally do not have the ability to replicate themselves like viruses; however, they can lead to other malware being installed on a machine, various data being stolen, or other malicious activities.</string>
  <string name="avast_virus_type_unknown_description">Tipo de infecção desconhecida</string>
  <string name="avast_virus_type_worm_description">Este vírus é um worm. It is a standalone malware that replicates itself in order to spread to other devices. Takes advantage of file or information transport features of system (such like network), it can travel without any human action. Worms almost always cause at least some harm to the network.</string>
  <string name="avl_dialog_dbupdate"/>
  <string name="avl_dialog_header">Esta funcionalidade encripta e envia o ID do seu dispositivo para os servidores AVL(%s)</string>
  <string name="avl_dialog_policy">Ver Política de Privacidade</string>
  <string name="avl_dialog_title">Política de Privacidade de AVL</string>
  <string name="avl_dialog_url">http://api.sec.miui.com/policy/proxy?p=antiy&amp;l=en_US</string>
  <string name="default_sdcard_volume_path"/>
  <string name="hello_world">Olá mundo!</string>
  <string name="menu_settings">Definições</string>
  <string name="tencent_dialog_cloudscan">Enviar e verificar os nomes e detalhes das aplicações utilizando definições de vírus online</string>
  <string name="tencent_dialog_dbupdate">Actualizar definições de vírus automaticamente</string>
  <string name="tencent_dialog_header">Esta funcionalidade encripta e envia o ID do seu dispositivo para os servidores Tencent(%s)</string>
  <string name="tencent_dialog_policy">Ver Política de Privacidade</string>
  <string name="tencent_dialog_title">Política de Privacidade de Tencent</string>
  <string name="tencent_dialog_url">http://api.sec.miui.com/policy/proxy?p=tencent&amp;l=en_US</string>
  <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>
</resources>
